Labor Song Books 5189
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Lyrics to "Eleanor Roosevelt Joes", Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Lyrics to "Eleanor Roosevelt Jones", Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Sne sheet of lyrics. Item is in English.
- Songs of rebellion, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
  [New Orleans: John J. Weighing Print. Co., c1915]
  - Item 1: Songs of rebellion, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Songs for Union Hall and Picket Line, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  TWUA-CIO
  - Item 1: Sunday in the park, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Textile Workers Song Book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Workers Song Book no. 2, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
    By Workers Music League. Item is in English.
- Workers Song Book No.2, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Good Chants for a Lively Picketline, Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
    By Ruth Goldbaum. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Good Chants for a Lively Picketline, Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Good Chants for a Lively Picket Line (and some great songs, too), Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Song Book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
    By Union Label and Service Trades Department. Item is in English.
- Song Book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Hit the Road, Bush: Songs for Regime Change, Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    By Mike Konopacki. Item is in English.
- Hit the Road Bush, Songs for Regime Change, 2004; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The ACTWU Songbook, Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union). Item is in English.
- The ACTWU Songbook, Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Hoot Song Sheet, Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
    By Teachers Union Local 555. Item is in English.
- Hoot Song Sheet, 1947; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Picket Line Songs, 1947; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Songs for America, 1939; Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Down in a Coal Mine: Songs and Chorus (phonograph disc, box 3 ff15 of 6118 AV), Publication (Box 5)
  - Down in a Coal Mine: Songs and Chorus by J.B. Geoghegan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    [phonograph disc - in box 3, ff15 of 6118 AV]
  - Peoples Songs - vol. 1, no.1-8,10-12 (1946-1947), Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Transferred from the Music Library
  - People's Songs - vol. 1, no. 10-12; vol. 2, no. 1-5 (1946-1947), Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - UAW-CIO Sings (2 versions); Quotations by the Great Men of the Ages; TWUA Songs, 1948-1949; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)